l don't know. I think
you might look sexy with long hair.
With the kind
that flows down to your shoulders...
(Amy:)...and blows back
while riding on a horse.
(Amy:)Bareback and bare-chested.
(Amy:)I'm gonna go brush my teeth,
it might take a while.
(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Hi, sweetie.
- l miss you.
- l miss you too.
(Bernadette:)So tell me all about your first day.
(Howard:)Oh, wow, where do I even start?
l got to experience zero gravity.
- Cool. How do they do that?
- It's pretty neat.
(Howard:)You get in this plane that goes
almost straight up for like 20 seconds...
(Howard:)...and then straight back down
like it's gonna crash...
(Howard:)...and they do it over and over again,
no matter how many times you throw up.